Viewers, I want to assure you that Jesus is as close to you as He was to Lazarus.
You all know what happened to the dead man; you know what happened to blind Bartimaeus.
Jesus is as close to you as He was to blind Bartimaeus.
It is time now for you to take from God the faith He has prepared to give you.
I believe; help my unbelief!
When the father of the demon-possessed boy came to Him, this was his voice -
he said he believed but his belief could not receive,
that shows that his belief was equal to unbelief.
Viewers, say after me, "I believe; help my unbelief!"
I can't hear you.
I believe; help my unbelief!
Viewers all over the world, listen:
Viewers all over the world:
I believe; help my unbelief!
In Jesus Christ's name.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Yes.
I will talk to you as I am hearing from Heaven.
I will not stand here and begin to say a word of mine. It is not mine - what I am about to say.
This is the voice of God, listen:
When we are disconnected from the devil, we are connected to God.
It is not possible to not be connected to either God or satan.
You cannot live in a neutral world.
Right now, you are about to be disconnected and be connected to God.
Whatever satan might have used to connect you - out, in Jesus' name!
How can satan connect us? You can be connected through poverty.
When poverty comes, you begin to look at Jesus in a bad light.
Whatever satan might have used to connect you -
satan's connection be broken, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
You know how you are connected.
You know your weakness, the area where you are not strong,
the area you complain about,
the area you talk about all the time - you are murmuring, complaining and doubting.
Whatever demons might have used to connect you to themselves, be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Every chain of demon, chain of affliction, chain of disappointment,
chain of sickness and disease -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In your heart - within and out, evil thoughts -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I am married to Jesus satan leave me alone
My Husband is coming to take me away
To everlasting home
I command healing on you!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command healing on you!
Every area, every faculty, every organ that has stopped functioning, begin to function!
Begin to function!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
It could be your kidneys, liver, blood, bones, your muscles -
begin to function, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, open your lips and begin to thank Jesus for taking you out of the affliction.
I thank You, Lord Jesus!
I thank You for taking me out of affliction, out of pain, out of hardship,
out of disappointment, out of rejection and out of hatred.
Open your lips!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Urinated Poisonous Substances During Viewers' Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
Fibroid Bursts During Viewers' Prayer
Watch your screen.
For you to know how mighty the anointing is.
The anointing is so mighty. Look at the fibroid.
Do you see the fibroid among you?
I am talking to the viewers all over the world but you in the church are receiving out of the viewers' blessings.
Then what do you think will happen to the viewers?
Tell me - what will happen to the viewers?
Fibroid Bursts During Viewers' Prayer
Hallelujah!
Listen, satan, you must remove your hand.
Remove your hand from my people!
Your hand of affliction, setback, sickness, disease, rejection, nightmares - remove your hand!
Remove your hand!
I say, "Remove your hand!"
Tell your neighbour: I say, "Remove your hand in the name of Jesus!"
I say, "Remove your hand from my life - your hand of affliction, setback, sickness, and disease!"
I say, "Remove your hand!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see satan removing his hand - never again, in Jesus' name!
Amen!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
To God be the glory! Watch the screen of your television!
As the man of God was praying just now, you can see the power of God moving in the life of the people.
You see a lady here, a fibroid just fell instantly out from her body when the man of God was praying.
Let us listen to her directly and hear what she has to say.
People of God, Emmanuel!
(Matthew 1:23 - God With Us)
My name is Mrs Chidinma Christian Gilbert.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was severe fibroids.
I had this problem for a very long time; I would have pain all over my body.
Immediately as the man of God was praying to the viewers all over the world,
I just found out that something burst out.
This is the first time I am seeing blood coming out of me like this.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus; I am free!
Can you press your stomach now? You said you could not press it before. How do you feel right now?
I feel very light. I am okay now; there is no more pain.
What happened is that the passage has been opened.
Any moment from now, she will feel pressed and go to the toilet.
The whole thing (will come out).
Right now, she will be having stomach pain.
But any moment she goes to the toilet, everything will be flushed out.
To God be the glory. While the prayer for the viewers was going on,
many people started vormiting different substances out of their system.
You saw the woman whose fibroid burst open and she started bleeding instantly.
Here is a woman who vomited a mixture of blood and other substances.
We just want to take one more to listen to and afterwards, we shall proceed.
Madam, tell us your name and the problem that brought you to The SCOAN.
My name is Ngozi Emmanuel Akeh.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a gunshot in the dream.
After the gunshot, I started having pain in my chest, my back, and all over my body like a moving object.
While the man of God was praying, I had the urge to vomit
because my stomach was turning and I vomited all these substances -
a mixture of blood and other substances.
Now, I am free. Thank You, Jesus! I am healed; I am delivered! No more pain in my stomach!
Now after the vomiting, how do you feel?
No more chest pain. I was even testing it before but i am okay; I cannot feel the pain anymore.
I was having pain from my chest, hands, legs, and nails - right now, I am okay!
I feel the pain no more!
Amen! Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Vomited Blood And Poisonous Substances During Viewers' Prayer
Healed During Viewers' Prayer